glozal.com 2017-09-10

# Privacy - GLOZAL- Social Media ID Number

Effective August 1, 2017  
This Privacy Policy Summary highlights how GLOZAL uses the information collected through its websites and online Privacy services.

Protecting personally identifying information is a core GLOZAL value. This Privacy Statement describes how GLOZAL collects and uses the personally identifying information you provide on our Web sites and on GLOZAL Internet applications that appear on third party websites. It also describes the choices available to you regarding GLOZAL's use of your personally identifying information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or delete it.

GLOZAL abides by the Safe Harbor Principles as set forth by the US Department of Commerce concerning the transfer of personal data from the European Union.

We self-certify compliance with

GLOZAL PROGRAMS AND SERVICES

If you apply to become a GLOZAL member, we will use the personally identifying information you provide (e.g., your name, address, email address, company information and payment information) to follow up with you about your application and facilitate the certification process.

We also use this information to provide you with customer support and to communicate regularly with you. While providing you with customer support we may also gather additional information from you. From time to time we will also offer you the opportunity to receive information about privacy-related products or services offered by our third-party partners. We will not share your personally identifying information with these third parties for their marketing purposes, unless we have your permission to do so.

We use information submitted through our Web site or collected through email or hard copy surveys to analyze the characteristics of our customers and improve our services. We will occasionally provide anonymzed aggregated statistics about our ID holders in reports made available to them, to third parties, or to the general public. These reports will not identify individual GLOZAL holders.

If you wish to sign up for GLOZAL programs, or to simply obtain information about GLOZAL program and services, we will collect your name, email address, phone number, and additional information. We use this information to contact you about your request, to assist you in the application process or to follow up with you about the programs and services in which you have expressed an interest.

GLOZAL COMMUNICATIONS  
If you sign up for GLOZAL newsletters, webinars, opt-out reminder e-mails, or other communications or you want to contact us generally, we will collect your contact information to fulfill your request. To unsubscribe, follow the unsubscribe link that appears at the end of each communication.

### Tracking Technologies

COOKIES  
Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. We use cookies on our site to:

  * help you navigate our website
  * facilitate the sign up and login process for our services
  * personalize your experience
  * analyze which pages our site visitors visit
  * provide website feature such as social sharing widgets and videos

Videos and other features on our site use Flash cookies to collect and store your preferences such as volume.  Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here:

Please note that some cookies may be placed by a third party service provider who performs some of these functions for us.

INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED BY OUR SITE  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather Web server log file information automatically such as your IP address, browser type, device type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to administer our website, understand how visitors navigate through our Site and to enhance your experience while using our Site.

HOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION  
We may provide your personally identifying information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as web site analytics or offering customer service. These third parties are authorized to use your personally identifying information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may also disclose your personally identifying information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process   To the extent we are legally permitted to do so, we will take commercially reasonable steps to notify you in the event that we are required to provide your personal information to third parties as part of legal process. when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a written government request if GLOZAL becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personally identifying information becomes subject to a different privacy statement  to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

We will share your personally identifying information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Statement. We do not otherwise sell your personally identifying information to third parties.

### Other Information

ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION  
To review and update your personally identifying information to ensure it is always accurate visit your profile information on a regular schedule.

SECURITY  
Providing security for the personally identifying information you submit via our Site is a priority for GLOZAL. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to; or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction; of your personally identifying information. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt the transmission of data on the GLOZAL ID holder application, payment and login pages. Please be aware, however, that no transmission of information via the Internet can be entirely secure. You should, therefore, always use caution when submitting personally identifying information online.

OUR MOTTO  
Your Privacy is Our Priority!

LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES  
This Privacy Statement applies to GLOZAL web services only. Our Site includes links to other Web sites. If you submit personally identifying information to any of those sites, your information is subject to their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT  
Please note that this Privacy Statement may change from time to time. If we change this privacy statement in ways that affect how we use your personally identifying information, we will advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes. We will also post a notice on our home page that this Privacy Statement has changed.
